I said gay in a song, now I'm a criminal Try to teach some history, now I'm political They banned my books, burned my words Guess free speech is just for birds Tried to play a show in Tampa Bay But the venue vanished yesterday No dancing here, no drag, no fun Your freedom's take, just hold a gun Can't play it in the panhandle No more too loud, too proud, too real, too ignore They locked the amps and boarded the door
Filed under woke and dangerous trash Sing it loud before they smash Your busted boombox of free speech More renal rights, more fascist vibes One man's feel is another's life They ban what's brown, they ban what's queer They ban whatever they don't wanna hear Now state, now state, now shade your say Since you swindled different pay While sticking straight, you'll find out quit It's too late Don't say gay, don't say black
Don't say science, don't fight back.
Don't read books, don't grow weed.
Don't you dare teach kids to fake or race.
Ban like facts in a school debate.
Ban like dark they use to celebrate.
Ban like hope behind a gaze.
So crank it loud, disturb the peace.
Make dissenters call the police.
Root bandit, foreigner.
Why chew weed or what now?
Play it louder, this song is bandit fighter.